# **GWACHUKWU IKENNA ELEBEKE**

10B Latunde Close, Ago Palace Way, Okota, Lagos. +2347030821996 / +2348153045001

gwachukwuelebeke@gmail.com

Github: https://github.com/gwachukwu LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/gwachukwu Portfolio: https://gwachukwu.github.io/Portfolio

#### PROFILE

Full -stack web developer with experience working with HTML, CSS3/SASS, JavaScript, React, NodeJS, ExpressJS, NoSQL (MongoDB) and SQL (Postgres), I build amazing and user-friendly web applications. I am also skilled in Computer Networking (Routing and Switching), Microsoft Azure, Sales and Customer Service. I enjoy working on new products, and occasionally taking on new challenges that push me to grow.

#### SKILLS

## Web Development

HTML, CSS3, SASS, VANILLA JAVASCRIPT, REACT, JSX, REDUX, PHP

NODEJS, EXPRESS, SQL (Postgres, MySQL), NoSQL (MongoDB).

## **Computer Networking**

Network engineering, Routing protocols (EIGRP, OSPF, BGP

Operational support, Multicasting knowledge (IPv4 and IPv6), Virtual networking, TCP/IP, NAT, ACL etc.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Software Developer Aug 2020 - present

Cerebre Digital Limited, Opebi, Ikeja, Lagos State.

- Full stack development with HTML5, CSS3/SASS, JavaScript, React, Node.js, PHP
- Use MySQL and PostgreSQL for database development
- Build software that meet clients' specifications

#### Software Engineer Nov 2019 – Aug 2020

Stutern Graduate Accelerator, Gbagada, Lagos State.

- Full stack development with HTML5, CSS3/SASS,
- Bootstrap4, React, NodeJS, Express.
- Used PostgreSQL/MongoDB for databases development.
- Developed and designed Restful API.
- Collaborating on GitHub, Trello and Slack.

## Information and Communications Technology Instructor 2018 KingChuks College Okota, Lagos State

- Managed institution's ICT networks and infrastructures
- Taught ICT as a subject.

### National Youth Service Corps: Educational Instructor 2016-2017

Gaskiya Model School, Katsina, Katsina State.

- Developed good mentoring and instructional skills
- **Taught Physics and Chemistry**

#### **TRAININGS**

# **SheHacks Africa Cohort 13 09/2019** (Access bank, Waaw and ACT foundations scholarship)

Web Development - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP. MvSQL.

Leadership and Entrepreneurship training

# **Andela Learning Community with Google** 05/2020

Google Africa Developer Scholarship (Mobile Web Specialist)

# **Andela Learning Community with** Microsoft 06/2020

Microsoft Azure Training Program

#### **PROJECTS**

Magnitude: React, Node.is, Express, Postgres.

Event centers application.

https://magnitude-event-centers.netlify.app

Sound Vault: React, NodeJS, Express, MongoDB.

Audio cloud service application. https://sound-vault.netlify.app

Gwachukwu's bank: React, NodeJS,

Express, MongoDB. A finance tracking app.

https://gwachukwus-bank.netlify.app

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Cisco Certified Network Associate (Routing and Switching) 2019

Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals 2020

#### **ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION**

BSc. Industrial Chemistry University of Benin, Benin city, Edo State, Nigeria 2015